arrowheadcu.org 2003-06-21

# Arrowhead Credit Union

**Privacy Policy**

**Arrowhead Credit Union Respects our Members' Right to Privacy**

**Protecting Your Privacy**   
Arrowhead Central Credit Union values the privacy of our members. You have chosen to do business with us, and we recognize our duty to keep the information you provide to us secure and confidential. We believe that all personal and financial information specific to you that you provide to the Credit Union through any channel constitutes personal information. Protecting your privacy, along with your financial assets, is at the core of our business. 

**Keeping Your Information Secure**  
Keeping your financial information secure is one of our most important responsibilities. We value your trust and handle your information with care. Our employees access information about you when needed to maintain your accounts or otherwise meet your needs. Our Service Standards emphasizes the importance of keeping our members' information confidential. We protect information according to established security standards and procedures, and we continually assess new technology for protecting information. 

**Working to Meet Your Needs Through Information**  
In the course of doing business, we collect and use various types of information, such as information available from public records, market research and credit reports, as well as information you provide to us. We may also access information about you, such as credit reports, when considering a request from you for additional services or when exercising our rights under the law or any agreement with you. 

**Keeping Information Accurate**  
Keeping your account information accurate and up to date is very important. We have established procedures so that your financial information is accurate, current and complete. If you ever find that your account information is incomplete, inaccurate or not current, please call or write us at the telephone number or address listed on your account statement. We will correct any wrong information as quickly as possible. 

**How \- and Why - Information is Shared**  
We limit who receives information and what type of information is shared. We share information with the goal of bringing you greater convenience and more choices.

**Sharing information with Arrowhead Central Credit Union Affiliates**  
Arrowhead Central Credit Union owns a number of companies; Arrowhead Trust Incorporated, Arrowhead Financial Group Inc. and Sawyer Cook Insurance. All of these companies are dedicated to working together to provide the products and services that you want. All of these companies meet the same stringent requirements to protect your privacy as the Credit Union. 

We may also share information from your applications with external sources, such as check printing and data processing companies. These companies might, for example, assist us in offering you certain products and services or help us mail statements. These companies act on our behalf and are required to keep the information that we provide to them confidential.

All vendors and service providers sign confidentiality agreements with Arrowhead Central Credit Union that prohibit them from using member information for any purpose other than that for which they have been contracted. We do not sell our member lists to catalogs, direct mail companies, magazines or other non-financial service providers. 

**How does Arrowhead Central Credit Union use cookies?**  
"Cookies" are elements of data that a website can send to your browser and store on your computer. Our cookies do not collect or contain personal information about you or compromise the confidentiality of your personal information.

Our system automatically gathers information about the areas you visit on our sites and about the links you may select from within our site to other areas of the Internet or elsewhere online. We use such information in the aggregate to understand how our users as a group use the services and resources provided on our sites. This way we know which areas of our sites are favorites of our users, which areas need improvement, and what technologies are being used so that we may continually improve our sites. We reserve the right in the future to link such usage information to Contact Information or Personal Nonpublic Information in order to securely verify your identity, to personalize aspects of your experience on our web sites and to better understand which information or services are of greater value to our customers.

We may share aggregated statistical information with our partners, suppliers and other third parties, but we will not share any individual names, personal navigational or other personal information.   
You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. You can also erase cookies already stored on your computer. If you choose not to accept these cookies or if you erase them, your experience at our site and other web sites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended. For more information on working with cookies, you should consult the User Manual, FAQ or Help function of your specific browser and operating system software.

While you are browsing our web sites, you might be directed to web sites operated by third parties. These other web sites may send their own cookies to you and collect data or solicit personal information. We do not control and are not responsible for what third parties do on their separate web sites, or how they handle information about you. 

**Other**  
Information may be exchanged with credit bureaus and similar organizations, provided when legally required or permitted, or in connection with a fraud investigation.

If we receive a subpoena or similar legal process demanding release of any information about you, we will generally attempt to notify you (unless we believe we are prohibited from doing so.) Except as required by law or as described above, we do not share information with other parties, including government agencies. 

Certain information, such as trust and fiduciary information is subject to very strict limitations regarding the sharing of information, both internally and externally. 

We do not collect personal identifying information about visitors to our Internet site. Individual visitors to Arrowhead Central Credit Union's web site remain anonymous. Our servers collect standard non-identifying information about visits to the site, such as date and time visited, IP address, city, state, and country. This information is used to compile standard statistics on site use. 

**Opt-Out Process**  
We believe our members should have the right to decline disclosure of personal information that is collected on our databases. The records for those individuals who request that their personal information not be used for future mailings or phone calls will be marked in our database so that their names will be excluded from any contact in the future. 

"Do not mail" excludes the member's name from all direct mail campaigns.   
"Do not call,” indicates that the member does not wish to receive any phone communication from (i.e., phone research or telemarketing campaigns) from Arrowhead Central Credit Union or its companies.   
“Do not email” excludes the member’s name from all Internet marketing campaigns.

**Request for Removal from Special Mailing Lists**  
If you wish to be taken off our account mailing and telemarketing lists for marketing and promotional offers, simply fill out this form and send it to Arrowhead Credit Union, PO Box 735, San Bernardino, CA 92402. Or fax it to (909) 882-0895 or email the form to [info@arrowheadcu.org](mailto:info@arrowheadcu.org). Please allow 3 to 4 weeks for your request to take effect. Once your request has been processed, it will remain in effect until you request a change.  

I prefer not to receive (check all that apply): 

__ Mail containing marketing and promotional offers.

__ Phone calls presenting marketing and promotional offers.

__ Email presenting marketing and promotional offers.

My Arrowhead Credit Union account number(s) are:

_______________________________________

_______________________________________

Member Name (Please Print) ______________________________

Member Address ________________________________________

City _________________ State ________ Zip_____________

Home Phone Number _________________________________
